<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>LibrePCB</title>
    <link>http://librepcb.org/</link>
    <description>Blog posts of LibrePCB, an Open Source EDA software</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://librepcb.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>LibrePCB Blog</title>
      <link>http://librepcb.org/blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <dc:creator></dc:creator>
      <guid>http://librepcb.org/blog/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Posts</title>
      <link>http://librepcb.org/post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <dc:creator></dc:creator>
      <guid>http://librepcb.org/post/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comparison with other EDA tools</title>
      <link>http://librepcb.org/compare/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <dc:creator></dc:creator>
      <guid>http://librepcb.org/compare/</guid>
      <description>Of course people compare LibrePCB to other EDA tools, especially Eagle and KiCad. To help you deciding which EDA tool is best for your needs, here a short overview about the differences between LibrePCB and other EDA tools.
Library Concept One major advantage of LibrePCB is the powerful library concept. See this talk at FOSDEM (slides here) for details.
LibrePCB vs. Eagle  LibrePCB is free of charge – without limitations, even for commercial usage LibrePCB has an integrated library manager, thus it&amp;rsquo;s much easier to install and update libraries LibrePCB library and project files are better suited for version control The schematic- and board editors of Eagle are currently more powerful (LibrePCB does not yet support hierarchical sheets, 3D view and more)  LibrePCB vs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discuss</title>
      <link>http://librepcb.org/discuss/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <dc:creator></dc:creator>
      <guid>http://librepcb.org/discuss/</guid>
      <description>Forum The best way for discussing improvement ideas or getting help is our discussion forum. Sign up and join the conversation!
Chat We also have a development channel on IRC and a group on Telegram. The two chats are bridged, so you can join any one of them to see all conversations.
 #librepcb on Freenode LibrePCB_dev on Telegram  Note that the chat is mainly for discussing the development of LibrePCB.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Donate to LibrePCB</title>
      <link>http://librepcb.org/donate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <dc:creator></dc:creator>
      <guid>http://librepcb.org/donate/</guid>
      <description>LibrePCB is an open source project – it&amp;rsquo;s made by the community, for the community. This means that everyone can use LibrePCB without paying for it.
But if you like LibrePCB, please consider supporting the ongoing development of LibrePCB with a donation. The more donations are made, the more time we can put into the development of new features to make LibrePCB even more powerful.
Ordering PCBs at AISLER You want to order a PCB designed with LibrePCB?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LibrePCB Downloads</title>
      <link>http://librepcb.org/download/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <dc:creator></dc:creator>
      <guid>http://librepcb.org/download/</guid>
      <description>Here you can download official LibrePCB releases.
Please read the Getting Started Guide for installation and usage instructions.
Windows Download LibrePCB Installer for Windows Alternative: Portable ZIP (extract &amp;amp; run)
Linux Download LibrePCB Installer for Linux Alternatives for various distributions: Snap, Flatpak, AppImage (set executable flag &amp;amp; run) or binary archive.
Arch Linux: librepcb (builds from source) or librepcb-appimage (downloads binary)
OpenPandora: librepcb from OpenPandora Repository
NixOS: librepcb package
BSD FreeBSD: librepcb port</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
